[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Julie Child, known to many as The French Chef, was not French.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where was Omar Sharif, one of the most famous Egyptian actors, born?", "correct_answer": "Alexandria, Egypt", "incorrect_answers": ["Paris, France", "New York City, USA", "Hamburg, Germany"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Does Luxembourg, a small landlocked country situated in the north-west of continental Europe, have three official languages: French, German and Luxembourgish?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which dress sizes are for those 5 2 - 5 3 tall, with an average bust but a shorter back?", "correct_answer": "Miss Petite sizes", "incorrect_answers": ["Womens sizes", "Half sizes", "Misses sizes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When a contestant selects the Daily Double on the game show Jeopardy! what is the least amount the player can wager?", "correct_answer": "$5", "incorrect_answers": ["$100", "$50", "$250"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does the term browning refer to in cooking?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Caramelization", "Removing excess fat from meat by heating", "Maillard reaction"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the symbol for Vanadium?", "correct_answer": "V", "incorrect_answers": ["Vd", "Vn", "Va"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A ghost is a supernatural entity thought to be the spirit of a person remaining on Earth after their death to seek revenge.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Chop Suey, a pasta dish consisting of short noodles, was originally made and served in which country?", "correct_answer": "USA", "incorrect_answers": ["Thailand", "China", "Vietnam"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Depression and anxiety are considered mood disorders.  Which of the following is also considered a mood disorder?", "correct_answer": "Bipolar Disorder", "incorrect_answers": ["Schizophrenia", "Schizotypal Personality Disorder", "Narcissism"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following did veteran pitcher Eddie Harris NOT use as a foreign substance to doctor the baseball in the movie Major League?", "correct_answer": "K-Y jelly", "incorrect_answers": ["Vagisil", "Crisco", "Bardol"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Barbary Wars were  fought between the USA and pirates from this part of the world.", "correct_answer": "The Mediterranean Coast of Africa", "incorrect_answers": ["The Gulf of Mexico", "Somalia and its coast", "The Persian Gulf"]}]